<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<merger version="3"><dataSet aapt-namespace="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto" config="main$Generated" generated="true" ignore_pattern="!.svn:!.git:!.ds_store:!*.scc:.*:&lt;dir>_*:!CVS:!thumbs.db:!picasa.ini:!*~"><source path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res"/></dataSet><dataSet aapt-namespace="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto" config="main" generated-set="main$Generated" ignore_pattern="!.svn:!.git:!.ds_store:!*.scc:.*:&lt;dir>_*:!CVS:!thumbs.db:!picasa.ini:!*~:!&lt;dir>navigation"><source path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res"><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-ro/translations.xml" qualifiers="ro"><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"Sunteți sigur că doriți să părăsiți această conversație? Această conversație nu este publică și nu veți putea reveni fără o invitație."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"Sunteți sigur că vreți să părăsiți această cameră? Sunteți singura persoană de aici. Dacă o părasiți, nimeni nu se va mai putea alătura în viitor, inclusiv dumneavoastra."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"Sunteți sigur că vrei să părăsiți această cameră? Această cameră nu este publică și nu va veti putea alătura din nou fără o invitație."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_action">"Alegeți proprietari"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_subtitle">"Sunteți singurul proprietar al acestei camere. Trebuie să transferați proprietatea către o altă persoană înainte de a părăsi camera."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_title">"Transferați proprietatea"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"Sunteți sigur că vreți să părăsiți camera?"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-ru/translations.xml" qualifiers="ru"><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"Вы уверены, что хотите покинуть беседу? Эта беседа не является общедоступной, и вы не сможете присоединиться к ней без приглашения."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"Вы уверены, что хотите покинуть эту комнату? Здесь есть только вы. Если вы покинете комнату, никто не сможет присоединиться к ней в будущем, включая вас."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"Вы уверены, что хотите покинуть эту комнату? Эта комната не является общедоступной, и Вы не сможете присоединиться к ней без приглашения."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_action">"Назначить владельцев"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_subtitle">"Вы единственный владелец этой комнаты. Перед тем, как её покинуть, необходимо передать владение кому-нибудь другому."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_title">"Передача владения"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"Вы уверены, что хотите покинуть комнату?"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-zh-rTW/translations.xml" qualifiers="zh-rTW"><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"您確定要離開對話嗎？此對話不是公開的，如果沒有收到邀請，您無法重新加入。"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"您確定要離開聊天室嗎？這裡只有您一個人。如果您離開了，包含您在內的所有人都無法再進入此聊天室。"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"您確定要離開聊天室嗎？此聊天室不是公開的，如果沒有收到邀請，您無法重新加入。"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_action">"選擇擁有者"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_subtitle">"您是此聊天室的唯一擁有者。離開聊天室前，您必須將所有權移轉給其他人。"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_title">"轉移所有權"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"您確定要離開聊天室嗎？"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-it/translations.xml" qualifiers="it"><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"Vuoi davvero abbandonare questa conversazione? La conversazione non è pubblica e non potrai rientrare senza un invito."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"Sei sicuro di voler lasciare questa stanza? Sei l\'unica persona presente. Se esci, nessuno potrà unirsi in futuro, te compreso."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"Sei sicuro di voler lasciare questa stanza? Questa stanza non è pubblica e non potrai rientrare senza un invito."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_action">"Scegli i proprietari"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_subtitle">"Sei l\'unico proprietario di questa stanza. Devi trasferire la proprietà a qualcun altro prima di lasciare la stanza."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_title">"Trasferisci proprietà"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"Sei sicuro di voler lasciare la stanza?"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-cs/translations.xml" qualifiers="cs"><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"Opravdu chcete opustit tuto konverzaci? Tato konverzace není veřejná a bez pozvánky se k ní nebudete moci znovu připojit."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"Opravdu chcete opustit tuto místnost? Jste tu jediná osoba. Pokud odejdete, nikdo se v budoucnu nebude moci připojit, včetně vás."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"Opravdu chcete opustit tuto místnost? Tato místnost není veřejná a bez pozvánky se nebudete moci znovu připojit."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_action">"Vyberte vlastníky"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_subtitle">"Jste jediným vlastníkem této místnost. Než místnost opustíte, musíte vlastnictví převést na někoho jiného."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"Opravdu chcete opustit místnost?"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-in/translations.xml" qualifiers="in"><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"Apakah Anda yakin ingin keluar dari percakapan ini? Percakapan ini tidak umum dan Anda tidak akan dapat bergabung lagi tanpa undangan."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"Apakah Anda yakin ingin meninggalkan ruangan ini? Anda adalah orang satu-satunya di sini. Jika Anda pergi, tidak akan ada yang bisa bergabung di masa depan, termasuk Anda."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"Apakah Anda yakin ingin meninggalkan ruangan ini? Ruangan ini tidak umum dan Anda tidak akan dapat bergabung kembali tanpa undangan."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_action">"Pilih Pemilik"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_subtitle">"Anda adalah satu-satunya pemilik ruangan ini. Anda perlu mentransfer kepemilikan kepada orang lain sebelum Anda meninggalkan ruangan."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_title">"Pindahkan kepemilikan"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"Apakah Anda yakin ingin meninggalkan ruangan?"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-ja/translations.xml" qualifiers="ja"><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"本当にこの会話を退出しますか？この会話は非公開で、再度参加するには招待が必要です。"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"本当にこのルームを退出しますか？あなたが最後の一人であり、このルームには誰も参加することができなくなります。"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"ルームから退出してもよいですか？ このルームは非公開のため、参加しなおすには改めて招待される必要があります。"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_action">"所有者を選択"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_subtitle">"あなたがこのルームの唯一の所有者です。退出する前に所有権を他のユーザーへ譲与する必要があります。"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_title">"所有権の譲与"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"本当にこのルームを退出しますか？"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-el/translations.xml" qualifiers="el"><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"Είσαι σίγουρος ότι θέλεις να αποχωρήσεις από αυτή τη συζήτηση; Αυτή η συνομιλία δεν είναι δημόσια και δεν θα μπορείς να συμμετάσχεις ξανά χωρίς πρόσκληση."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"Είστε σίγουροι ότι θέλετε να αποχωρήσετε από αυτή την αίθουσα; Είστε το μόνο άτομο εδώ. Αν αποχωρήσετε, κανείς δεν θα μπορεί να ενταχθεί στο μέλλον, ούτε εσείς."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"Είστε σίγουροι ότι θέλετε να αποχωρήσετε από αυτήν την αίθουσα; Αυτή η αίθουσα δεν είναι δημόσια και δεν θα μπορέσετε να επανενταχτείτε χωρίς πρόσκληση."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_action">"Επιλέξτε ιδιοκτήτες"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_subtitle">"Είστε ο μόνος ιδιοκτήτης αυτής της αίθουσας. Πρέπει να μεταβιβάσετε την ιδιοκτησία σε κάποιον άλλο πριν φύγετε από την αίθουσα."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_title">"Μεταβίβαση ιδιοκτησίας"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"Είστε σίγουροι ότι θέλετε να αποχωρήσετε από την αίθουσα;"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-da/translations.xml" qualifiers="da"><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"Er du sikker på, at du vil forlade denne samtale? Denne samtale er ikke offentlig, og du kan ikke deltage igen uden en invitation."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"Er du sikker på, at du vil forlade dette rum? Du er den eneste person her. Hvis du går, vil ingen kunne tilslutte sig det i fremtiden, heller ikke dig."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"Er du sikker på, at du vil forlade dette rum? Rummet er ikke offentligt, så du vil ikke kunne deltage igen uden en invitation."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_action">"Vælg ejere"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_subtitle">"Du er den eneste ejer af dette rum. Du skal overføre ejerskabet til en anden, før du forlader rummet."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_title">"Overdrag ejerskab"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"Er du sikker på, at du ønsker at forlade rummet?"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-pt-rBR/translations.xml" qualifiers="pt-rBR"><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"Tem certeza de que deseja sair dessa conversa? Essa conversa não é pública e você não poderá entrar novamente sem um convite."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"Tem certeza de que deseja sair desta sala? Você é a única pessoa aqui. Se você sair, ninguém poderá entrar no futuro, até mesmo você."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"Tem certeza de que deseja sair desta sala? Esta sala não é pública e você não poderá entrar novamente sem um convite."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_action">"Escolher proprietários"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_subtitle">"Você é o único proprietário desta sala. Você precisa transferir a posse para outra pessoa antes de sair da sala."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_title">"Transferir posse"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"Tem certeza de que deseja sair da sala?"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-be/translations.xml" qualifiers="be"><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"Вы ўпэўнены, што хочаце пакінуць гэту размову? Гэта размова не з\'яўляецца публічнай, і вы не зможаце далучыцца зноў без запрашэння."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"Вы ўпэўнены, што хочаце пакінуць гэты пакой? Вы тут адзіны карыстальнік. Калі вы выйдзеце, ніхто не зможа далучыцца ў будучыні, у тым ліку і вы."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"Вы ўпэўнены, што хочаце пакінуць гэты пакой? Гэты пакой не агульнадаступны, і вы не зможаце далучыцца да яго зноў без запрашэння."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"Вы ўпэўнены, што хочаце пакінуць пакой?"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values/localazy.xml" qualifiers=""><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"Are you sure that you want to leave this conversation? This conversation is not public and you won\'t be able to rejoin without an invite."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"Are you sure that you want to leave this room? You\'re the only person here. If you leave, no one will be able to join in the future, including you."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"Are you sure that you want to leave this room? This room is not public and you won\'t be able to rejoin without an invite."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_action">"Choose owners"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_subtitle">"You\'re the only owner of this room. You need to transfer ownership to someone else before you leave the room."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_title">"Transfer ownership"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"Are you sure that you want to leave the room?"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-uz/translations.xml" qualifiers="uz"><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"Bu suhbatni tark etmoqchi ekanligingizga ishonchingiz komilmi? Bu suhbat hammaga ochiq emas va siz taklifsiz qayta qo‘shila olmaysiz."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"Bu xonani tark etmoqchi ekanligingizga ishonchingiz komilmi? Siz bu yerda yagona odamsiz. Agar siz tark etsangiz, kelajakda hech kim qo\'shila olmaydi, jumladan siz ham."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"Bu xonani tark etmoqchi ekanligingizga ishonchingiz komilmi? Bu xona ochiq emas va siz taklifsiz qayta qo‘shila olmaysiz."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_action">"Egalarni tanlang"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_subtitle">"Siz bu xonaning yagona egasisiz. Xonadan chiqishdan oldin egalikni boshqaga topshirishingiz kerak."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_title">"Egalikni topshirish"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"Xonani tark etmoqchi ekanligingizga ishonchingiz komilmi?"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-pl/translations.xml" qualifiers="pl"><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"Czy na pewno chcesz opuścić tę konwersację? Konwersacja nie jest publiczna i nie będziesz mógł dołączyć ponownie bez zaproszenia."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"Jesteś pewien, że chcesz opuścić ten pokój? Jesteś tu jedyną osobą. Jeśli wyjdziesz, nikt nie będzie mógł dołączyć, w tym Ty."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"Czy na pewno chcesz opuścić ten pokój? Ten pokój nie jest publiczny i nie będziesz mógł do niego wrócić bez zaproszenia."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_action">"Wybierz właścicieli"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_subtitle">"Jesteś jedynym właścicielem tego pokoju. Musisz przenieść własność na kogoś innego, zanim go opuścisz."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_title">"Przenieś własność"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"Jesteś pewien, że chcesz wyjść z tego pokoju?"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-vi/translations.xml" qualifiers="vi"><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"Bạn có chắc chắn muốn rời khỏi cuộc trò chuyện này không? Cuộc trò chuyện này không công khai và bạn sẽ không thể tham gia lại nếu không được mời."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"Bạn có chắc chắn muốn rời khỏi phòng này không? Bạn là người duy nhất ở đây. Nếu bạn rời đi, sẽ không ai có thể tham gia nữa, kể cả bạn."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"Bạn có chắc chắn muốn rời khỏi phòng này không? Phòng này không công khai và bạn sẽ không thể tham gia lại nếu không có lời mời."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"Bạn có chắc chắn muốn rời khỏi phòng không?"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-sv/translations.xml" qualifiers="sv"><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"Är du säker på att du vill lämna den här konversationen? Den här konversationen är inte offentlig och du kommer inte att kunna gå med igen utan en inbjudan."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"Är du säker på att du vill lämna det här rummet? Du är den enda personen här. Om du lämnar kommer ingen att kunna gå med i framtiden, inklusive du."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"Är du säker på att du vill lämna det här rummet? Detta rum är inte offentligt och du kommer inte att kunna gå med igen utan en inbjudan."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_action">"Välj ägare"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_subtitle">"Du är den enda ägaren av det här rummet. Du måste överföra ägarskapet till någon annan innan du lämnar rummet."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_title">"Överför ägarskap"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"Är du säker på att du vill lämna rummet?"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-sk/translations.xml" qualifiers="sk"><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"Ste si istí, že chcete opustiť konverzáciu?"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"Ste si istí, že chcete opustiť túto miestnosť? Ste tu jediná osoba. Ak odídete, nikto sa do nej nebude môcť v budúcnosti pripojiť, vrátane vás."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"Ste si istí, že chcete opustiť túto miestnosť? Táto miestnosť nie je verejná a bez pozvania sa do nej nebudete môcť vrátiť."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_action">"Vybrať vlastníkov"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_subtitle">"Ste jediným vlastníkom tejto miestnosti. Pred opustením miestnosti musíte previesť vlastníctvo na niekoho iného."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_title">"Preniesť vlastníctvo"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"Ste si istí, že chcete opustiť miestnosť?"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-ur/translations.xml" qualifiers="ur"><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"کیا آپ واقعی اس گفتگو کو چھوڑنا چاہتے ہیں؟ یہ گفتگو عوامی نہیں ہے اور آپ دعوت نامے کے بغیر دوبارہ شامل نہیں ہو سکیں گے۔"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"کیا آپ واقعی یہ کمرہ چھوڑنا چاہتے ہیں؟ آپ یہاں واحد شخص ہیں۔ اگر آپ چھوڑتے ہیں، تو مستقبل میں کوئی بھی شامل نہیں ہو سکے گا، آپ سمیت۔"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"کیا آپ واقعی یہ کمرہ چھوڑنا چاہتے ہیں؟ یہ کمرہ عوامی نہیں اور آپ دعوت نامے کے بغیر پھر شامل نہیں ہو پائیں گے۔"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"کیا آپ واقعی کمرہ چھوڑنا چاہتے ہیں؟"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-tr/translations.xml" qualifiers="tr"><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"Bu sohbetten ayrılmak istediğinizden emin misiniz? Bu sohbet herkese açık değil ve davet olmadan tekrar katılamayacaksınız."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"Bu odadan ayrılmak istediğinizden emin misiniz? Burada tek kişi sizsiniz. Ayrılırsanız, siz de dahil olmak üzere gelecekte kimse katılamayacak."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"Bu odadan ayrılmak istediğinizden emin misiniz? Bu oda herkese açık değildir ve davet olmadan tekrar katılamazsınız."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_action">"Sahipleri seçin"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_subtitle">"Bu odanın tek sahibisiniz. Odadan çıkmadan önce sahipliği başka birine devretmelisiniz."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_title">"Sahipliği aktar"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"Odadan çıkmak istediğinden emin misin?"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-fa/translations.xml" qualifiers="fa"><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"مطمئنید که می‌خواهید این اتاق را ترک کنید؟ تنها فرد این‌جا هستید. در صورت ترک، هیچ‌کسی از جمله خودتان در آینده نخواهد توانست به آن بپیوندد."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"مطمئنید که می‌خواهید این اتاق را ترک کنید؟ این اتاق عمومی نبوده قادر نخواهید بود بدون دعوت دوباره بپیوندید."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_action">"گزینش مالکان"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_title">"انتقال مالکیت"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"مطمئنید که می‌خواهید این اتاق را ترک کنید؟"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-lt/translations.xml" qualifiers="lt"><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"Ar tikrai norite išeiti iš šio kambario? Jūs esate vienintelis žmogus jame. Jei išeisite, niekas negalės prisijungti ateityje, įskaitant Jus."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"Ar tikrai norite išeiti iš šio kambario? Šis kambarys nėra viešas ir negalėsite vėl prisijungti be kvietimo."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"Ar tikrai norite išeiti iš kambario?"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-cy/translations.xml" qualifiers="cy"><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"Ydych chi\'n siŵr eich bod am adael y sgwrs hon? Dyw\'r sgwrs hon ddim yn gyhoeddus a fyddwch chi ddim yn gallu ailymuno heb wahoddiad."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"Ydych chi\'n siŵr eich bod am adael yr ystafell hon? Chi yw\'r unig berson yma. Os byddwch yn gadael, fydd neb yn gallu ymuno yn y dyfodol, gan gynnwys chi."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"Ydych chi\'n siŵr eich bod am adael yr ystafell hon? Dyw\'r ystafell hon ddim yn gyhoeddus a fyddwch chi ddim yn gallu ailymuno heb wahoddiad."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_action">"Dewiswch Berchnogion"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_subtitle">"Chi yw unig berchennog yr ystafell hon. Mae angen i chi drosglwyddo perchnogaeth i rywun arall cyn i chi adael yr room."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_title">"Trosglwyddo perchnogaeth"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"Ydych chi\'n siŵr eich bod am adael yr ystafell?"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-eu/translations.xml" qualifiers="eu"><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"Ziur elkarrizketa utzi nahi duzula? Ez da publikoa eta ezingo zara berriro batu gonbidapenik gabe."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"Ziur gelatik irten nahi duzula? Dagoen pertsona bakarra zara. Ateratzen bazara ezingo da inor batu etorkizunean, ezta zeu ere."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"Ziur gelatik irten nahi duzula? Gela hau ez da publikoa eta ezingo zara berriro batu gonbidapenik gabe."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_action">"Aukeratu jabeak"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_title">"Eskualdatu jabetza"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"Ziur gelatik atera nahi duzula?"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-fi/translations.xml" qualifiers="fi"><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"Haluatko varmasti poistua keskustelusta? Tämä keskustelu ei ole julkinen ja et voi liittyä takaisin ilman kutsua."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"Haluatko varmasti poistua huoneesta? Olet huoneen ainoa jäsen. Jos poistut, kukaan ei voi liittyä takaisin, et edes sinä."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"Haluatko varmasti poistua huoneesta? Tämä huone ei ole julkinen ja et voi liittyä takaisin ilman kutsua."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_action">"Valitse omistajat"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_subtitle">"Olet tämän huoneen ainoa omistaja. Sinun on siirrettävä omistajuus jollekulle toiselle ennen kuin poistut huoneesta."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_title">"Siirrä omistajuus"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"Haluatko varmasti poistua huoneesta?"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-fr/translations.xml" qualifiers="fr"><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"Êtes-vous sûr de vouloir quitter cette discussion ? Vous ne pourrez pas la rejoindre à nouveau sans y être invité."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"Êtes-vous sûr de vouloir quitter ce salon ? Vous êtes la seule personne ici. Si vous partez, personne ne pourra rejoindre le salon à l’avenir, y compris vous."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"Êtes-vous sûr de vouloir quitter ce salon ? Ce salon n’est pas public et vous ne pourrez pas le rejoindre sans invitation."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_action">"Choisir les propriétaires"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_subtitle">"Vous êtes le seul propriétaire de ce salon. Vous devez en transférer la propriété à quelqu’un d’autre avant de le quitter."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_title">"Transférer la propriété"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"Êtes-vous sûr de vouloir quitter le salon ?"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-es/translations.xml" qualifiers="es"><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"¿Estás seguro de que quieres salir de esta conversación? Esta conversación no es pública y no podrás volver a unirte sin una invitación."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"¿Estás seguro de que quieres salir de esta sala? Eres la única persona aquí. Si te vas, nadie podrá unirse en el futuro, ni siquiera tú."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"¿Seguro que quieres salir de esta sala? Esta sala no es pública y no podrás volver a entrar sin una invitación."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"¿Seguro que quieres salir de la sala?"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-et/translations.xml" qualifiers="et"><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"Kas sa oled kindel, et soovid sellest vestlusest lahkuda? See vestlus pole avalik ja uuesti liitumiseks vajad kutset."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"Kas sa oled kindel, et soovid sellest jututoast lahkuda? Sa oled siin viimane osaleja ja peale sinu lahkumist ei saa keegi enam liituda, isegi sina mitte."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"Kas sa oled kindel, et soovid sellest jututoast lahkuda? See jututuba pole avalik ja uuesti liitumiseks vajad kutset."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_action">"Vali omanikud"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_subtitle">"Sa oled selle jututoa ainus omanik. Enne jututoast lahkumist pead omandi üle andma kellelegi teisele."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_title">"Anna omand üle"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"Kas sa oled kindel, et soovid sellest jututoast lahkuda?"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-hr/translations.xml" qualifiers="hr"><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"Jeste li sigurni da želite napustiti ovaj razgovor? Ovaj razgovor nije javan i nećete se moći ponovno pridružiti bez pozivnice."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"Jeste li sigurni da želite napustiti ovu sobu? Ovdje ste jedino vi. Ako odete, nitko se ubuduće neće moći pridružiti, pa ni vi."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"Jeste li sigurni da želite napustiti ovu sobu? Ova soba nije javna i nećete joj se moći ponovno pridružiti bez pozivnice."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_action">"Odaberi vlasnike"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_subtitle">"Vi ste jedini vlasnik ove sobe. Morate prenijeti vlasništvo na nekog drugog prije nego što napustite sobu."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_title">"Prenesi vlasništvo"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"Jeste li sigurni da želite napustiti sobu?"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-hu/translations.xml" qualifiers="hu"><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"Biztos, hogy elhagyja ezt a beszélgetést? Ez a beszélgetés nem nyilvános, és meghívás nélkül nem fog tudni visszacsatlakozni."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"Biztos, hogy elhagyja ezt a szobát? Ön az egyedüli ember itt. Ha kilép, akkor senki sem fog tudni csatlakozni a jövőben, Önt is beleértve."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"Biztos, hogy elhagyja ezt a szobát? Ez a szoba nem nyilvános, és meghívó nélkül nem fog tudni újra belépni."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_action">"Tulajdonosok kiválasztása"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_subtitle">"Ön az egyetlen tulajdonosa ennek a szobának. Mielőtt elhagyja a szobát, át kell adnia a tulajdonjogot valaki másnak."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_title">"Tulajdonjog átruházása"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"Biztos, hogy elhagyja a szobát?"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-nl/translations.xml" qualifiers="nl"><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"Weet je zeker dat je dit gesprek wilt verlaten? Dit gesprek is niet openbaar en je kunt niet opnieuw deelnemen zonder een uitnodiging."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"Weet je zeker dat je deze kamer wilt verlaten? Je bent de enige persoon hier. Als je weggaat, kan er in de toekomst niemand meer toetreden, ook jij niet."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"Weet je zeker dat je deze kamer wilt verlaten? Deze kamer is niet openbaar en je kunt niet opnieuw deelnemen zonder een uitnodiging."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"Weet je zeker dat je de kamer wilt verlaten?"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-bg/translations.xml" qualifiers="bg"><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"Сигурни ли сте, че искате да напуснете тази стая? Вие сте единственият човек тук. Ако напуснете, никой няма да може да се присъедини в бъдеще, включително и вие."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"Сигурни ли сте, че искате да напуснете тази стая? Тази стая не е общодостъпна и няма да можете да се присъедините отново без покана."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"Сигурни ли сте, че искате да напуснете стаята?"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-nb/translations.xml" qualifiers="nb"><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"Er du sikker på at du vil forlate denne samtalen? Denne samtalen er ikke offentlig, og du vil ikke kunne bli med igjen uten en invitasjon."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"Er du sikker på at du vil forlate dette rommet? Du er den eneste personen her. Hvis du forlater, vil ingen kunne bli med i fremtiden, inkludert deg."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"Er du sikker på at du vil forlate dette rommet? Dette rommet er ikke offentlig, og du vil ikke kunne bli med igjen uten en invitasjon."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_action">"Velg eiere"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_subtitle">"Du er den eneste eieren av dette rommet. Du må overføre eierskapet til noen andre før du forlater rommet."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_title">"Overfør eierskap"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"Er du sikker på at du vil forlate rommet?"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-ka/translations.xml" qualifiers="ka"><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"დარწმუნებული ხართ ამ საუბრის დატოვებაში? იგი საჯარო არაა და მოწვევის გარეშე ხელახლა ვერ შეურთდებით."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"დარწმუნებული ბრძანდებით, რომ ამ ოთახის დატოვება გსურთ? თქვენ აქ მარტო ხართ და ჩატის დატოვებისას აქ თქვენს ჩათვლით ვერავინ ვერ გაწევრიანდება."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"დარწმუნებული ბრძანდებით, რომ ამ ოთახის დატოვება გსურთ? ეს ოთახი არ არის საჯარო და მოწვევის გარეშე ვერ შეძლებთ ხელახლა გაწევრიანებას."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"დარწმუნებული ბრძანდებით, რომ ოთახის დატოვება გსურთ?"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-de/translations.xml" qualifiers="de"><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"Bist du sicher, dass du diese Unterhaltung verlassen willst? Diese Unterhaltung ist nicht öffentlich und du kannst ihr ohne Einladung nicht wieder beitreten."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"Bist du sicher, dass du diesen Chat verlassen möchtest? Du bist die einzige Person hier. Wenn du gehst, kann in Zukunft niemand mehr eintreten, auch du nicht."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"Bist du sicher, dass du diesen Chat verlassen möchtest? Dieser Chat ist nicht öffentlich und du kannst ihm ohne Einladung nicht erneut beitreten."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_action">"Wähle Eigentümer"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_subtitle">"Du bist der einzige Eigentümer dieses Chats. Du musst die Eigentumsrechte an jemand anderen übertragen, bevor du den Chat verlässt."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_title">"Eigentumsrechte übertragen"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"Bist du sicher, dass du den Chat verlassen willst?"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-ko/translations.xml" qualifiers="ko"><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"이 대화를 나가시겠습니까? 이 대화는 공개되지 않았으므로 초대 없이는 다시 참여할 수 없습니다."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"정말로 이 방을 떠나시겠어요? 이 방에서 유일하게 남은 사용자입니다. 나간 이후부터는 당신을 포함해서 아무도 다시 참여할 수 없어요."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"정말로 이 방을 떠나시겠어요? 이 방은 공개가 아니기 때문에 초대 없이는 다시 참여할 수 없습니다."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_action">"소유자 선택"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_subtitle">"이 방의 유일한 소유자는 귀하입니다. 방을 떠나기 전에 다른 사람에게 소유권을 양도해야 합니다."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_title">"소유권 이전"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"정말로 이 방을 떠나시겠어요?"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-pt/translations.xml" qualifiers="pt"><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"Tens a certeza que queres sair desta conversa? Não é pública, logo não poderás voltar a participar sem um convite."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"Tens a certeza que queres sair desta sala? És o único participante. Se saíres, ninguém mais poderá entrar, incluindo tu."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"Tens a certeza que queres sair desta sala? Atenta que não é pública e portanto não poderás voltar a entrar sem um novo convite."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_action">"Escolher donos"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_subtitle">"És o único dono/dona desta sala. Se quiseres sair, terás que a transferir para alguém primeiro."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_title">"Transferir posse"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"Tens a certeza que queres sair da sala?"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-zh/translations.xml" qualifiers="zh"><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"您确定要离开此对话吗？此对话不公开，未经邀请您将无法重新加入。"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"确定要离开此聊天室吗？此处只有你一个人。如果离开此聊天室，包括你在内的所有人都将无法进入。"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"确定要离开此聊天室吗？此聊天室不公开，没有邀请你将无法重新加入。"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_action">"选择所有者"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_subtitle">"您是本房间的唯一所有者。离开房间前，您需要将所有权转移给他人。"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_title">"转让所有权"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"确定要离开聊天室吗？"</string></file><file path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/main/res/values-uk/translations.xml" qualifiers="uk"><string name="leave_conversation_alert_subtitle">"Ви впевнені, що хочете залишити цю розмову? Ця розмова не загальнодоступна, і ви не зможете знову приєднатися без запрошення."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_empty_subtitle">"Ви впевнені, що хочете вийти з цієї кімнати? Ви тут єдина людина. Якщо ви вийдете, ніхто в майбутньому не зможе приєднатися, у тому числі й ви."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_private_subtitle">"Ви впевнені, що хочете вийти з цієї кімнати? Ця кімната не загальнодоступна, і ви не зможете повернутися до неї без запрошення."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_action">"Оберіть власників"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_subtitle">"Ви є єдиним власником цієї кімнати. Перед тим як вийти з кімнати, вам потрібно передати право власності іншій особі."</string><string name="leave_room_alert_select_new_owner_title">"Передати право власності"</string><string name="leave_room_alert_subtitle">"Ви впевнені, що хочете вийти з кімнати?"</string></file></source></dataSet><dataSet aapt-namespace="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto" config="debug$Generated" generated="true" ignore_pattern="!.svn:!.git:!.ds_store:!*.scc:.*:&lt;dir>_*:!CVS:!thumbs.db:!picasa.ini:!*~"><source path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/debug/res"/></dataSet><dataSet aapt-namespace="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto" config="debug" generated-set="debug$Generated" ignore_pattern="!.svn:!.git:!.ds_store:!*.scc:.*:&lt;dir>_*:!CVS:!thumbs.db:!picasa.ini:!*~:!&lt;dir>navigation"><source path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/src/debug/res"/></dataSet><dataSet aapt-namespace="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto" config="generated$Generated" generated="true" ignore_pattern="!.svn:!.git:!.ds_store:!*.scc:.*:&lt;dir>_*:!CVS:!thumbs.db:!picasa.ini:!*~"><source path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/build/generated/res/resValues/debug"/></dataSet><dataSet aapt-namespace="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto" config="generated" generated-set="generated$Generated" ignore_pattern="!.svn:!.git:!.ds_store:!*.scc:.*:&lt;dir>_*:!CVS:!thumbs.db:!picasa.ini:!*~:!&lt;dir>navigation"><source path="/Users/muskansethi/Documents/GitHub/whatsapp-clone-x-android/features/leaveroom/api/build/generated/res/resValues/debug"/></dataSet><mergedItems/></merger>